

Javier Turner

Print Production Estimator



Professional Summary

Creative and astute Full Stack Development graduate excelling in front end web development.

Self-motivated, dependable Production Estimator consistently rewarded for success in cost quoting and productivity improvements. Experience in policy development and maintaining positive customer relationships.



Work History

2018-10 -Current

Print Production Estimator

Classic Graphics, Charlotte, NC

Developed standard operating procedures and document workflows for current and future process steps

Delivered comprehensive bid proposals for projects and gained client approval on costs

Lead Estimator for clients who generate 35% of total company's revenue (Belk, SouthEastern Grocers, Gable)

2017-05 -2018-10

Wide Format Planner

Classic Graphics, Charlotte, NC

Worked with sales, pre-production, and production departments to implement corrective actions for missed milestones

Developed, released and monitored daily schedules to foster on-time completion of finished products Employed accurate forecasting to increase efficiency and reduce waste in department by 15%



Education

2019-10 -2020-04

Full-Stack Development

University of North Carolina at Charlotte

2014-08 -2017-05

Bachelor of Arts: Graphic Arts And Imaging Technology

Appalachian State University - Boone, NC



Address

Charlotte, NC

E-mail

javier.t.turner@gmail.com

LinkedIn

www.linkedin.com/in/javierturner



Skills

React

JavaScript

HTML5

Express

Node

MySQL

MongoDB

CSS

Adobe Creative Suite

JQuery

Digital print design knowledge

Storyboarding